(footsteps approaching)
(wood crashes)
That was a close
one! Are you all right?
Salmon.
Here it comes!
Stop it!
(bells ringing)
Convergence! Piercing Blood!
[Megumi] Did he wound it?
So he was holding back
when he fought me?
[Noritoshi] Hurry! Those
wounds'll heal quickly!
(footsteps departing)
(Inumaki gasps)
[Noritoshi]
Inumaki will stop it.
We'll attack, and then
we'll get away from it.
Then we'll repeat that as
we try to get outside this veil,
and rejoin the
principal and the others.
(wall crashes in)
[Noritoshi] But
there's no telling
when this current
balance will fall apart!
(dark music)
[Noritoshi] His cursed speech
doesn't seem to
be very effective,
and we're not getting a
chance to contact the teachers.
If it figures out how to
deal with his cursed speech,
we're finished.
(wood crashes)
(footsteps approaching)
Hurry!
(Megumi grunts)
[Noritoshi] We still don't know
what this cursed spirit's after!
It's possible the
principal and the sorcerers
stationed at Jujutsu Tech
haven't taken any action yet.
I'd like to join up with Todo.
Or at the very least, Miwa, but-
(door opens)
(intense music)
(wood crashes)
(Nue caws)
Inumaki will stop it
for you! Attack it now!
Stop!
-(blood splatters)
-(Noritoshi gasps)
(Inumaki gags)
[Noritoshi] He's the
one hitting his limit first?
(Noritoshi gasps)
(Noritoshi yells)
(Megumi grunts)
How're you doing,
Kamo? Still alive?
(dark music)
[Megumi] Inumaki wasn't
even using powerful words,
but it still
destroyed his throat!
This thing's just
that much stronger!
(dark music)
(Megumi gasps)
Mustard leaf.
Don't, Inumaki!
It's way too strong!
(footsteps approaching)
Blast away!
(wood crashes)
(Inumaki gags)
(dark music)
[Hanami] You can't hope to
cut me with that dull blade.
(Maki grunts)
(Megumi grunts)
(wood snaps)
(dark music)
[Megumi] Its eye
trees are more fragile
than the rest of it!
[Hanami] Now, that
sword isn't so bad.
(fast music)
I have something even better.
Though I have to say, using
this one feels disgusting.
(rock music)
[Kiyotaka] "Cursed tools" are
weapons imbued with curses.
Based on their force
and their effects,
they're divided into
grades one through four,
just like sorcerers.
The higher a
cursed tool's grade,
the greater the advantage
it provides its user
in jujutsu combat.
[Maki] Megumi, you'd
better not lose that!
[Megumi] Don't worry, I won't.
[Maki] It's probably worth
five billion if you sold it.
[Megumi] Huh?
[Maki] Special-grade
cursed tool: Playful Cloud!
(Hanami flies)
(rock music)
[Hanami] Indeed,
that is a good weapon.
-(footsteps approaching)
-(Megumi claps)
[Megumi] Demon Dog.
With the exception of
my expanded technique,
Bottomless Well,
if any of my ten shikigami
are completely destroyed,
I can never manifest them again!
(rock music)
[Megumi] However,
all of the power and techniques
of each of the
destroyed shikigami,
are passed on to the others!
(rock music)
[Megumi] Totality!
(Demon Dog roars)
(rock music)
[Hanami] It learns fast.
It's trying to take off
my wounded arm first.
The sorcerer boy
is in the forest.
(water splashing)
(Maki grunts)
(sword clangs)
(Hanami grunts)
[Hanami] The boy's sword!
(Megumi grunts)
Maki!
(Maki grunts)
(water splashing)
(Maki and Megumi grunt)
(Hanami gags)
Don't ever let me use
that three-piece staff again!
It's too hard!
Ah, you get used to-(gasp)
-Megumi!
-(Megumi gags)
(curse laughs)
(Maki gasps)
(Maki grunts)
[Megumi] Maki!
Damn it! All
because I screwed up!
(Maki grunts)
[Hanami] My strike was
aimed for your heart.
What a wonderful reaction.
Jujutsu sorcerers are so
extraordinarily compassionate.
As a result, an opening
is always created
when their ally is injured.
(water splashing)
-(Megumi groans)
-(Maki gasps)
[Maki] Was it destroyed?
No, Megumi released
the technique!
[Hanami] You shouldn't use
cursed techniques anymore.
The bud embedded in you
now, loves cursed energy.
So the more you use techniques,
the deeper its roots will
extend into your body.
What good's the warning?
If you're just gonna
kill us anyway?
[Hanami] Apparently, it
works faster when I explain it.
(Maki grunts)
[Hanami] You move well.
(Hanami punches)
(Maki chokes)
[Hanami] But, you're missing
the edge you had earlier.
(dark music)
[Megumi] I have to wring
out that cursed energy!
Even if it rips my stomach open!
I'm not like everyone else.
I choose who I protect!
I shoulder the
least responsibility!
Therefore,
I am simply not allowed
to fall before anyone else!
(Megumi gasps)
(Megumi yells)
[Maki] Megumi, stop!
[Megumi] Huh?
We did it! Our job here is done!
It's time to tag out.
(water splashes)
Huh?
(fast music)
Alright, friend. You good to go?
Yeah!
(opening theme music)
(singing in Japanese)
(music fades out)
(Momo groans)
(heavy breathing)
So heavy!
I can't believe these
two got beaten this badly!
Come on, Todo.
We need you.
Your strength is the one
thing you've got going for you.
(water running)
Forget it, Itadori!
You may think you can
handle that thing, but-
(Megumi gags)
Panda.
I'm right here.
Take these two and
get them out of the veil.
According to the
report from Nishimiya,
this is an anti-Gojo veil.
So the rest of us can come
and go without any issues.
-Wait! Not even you
can't- -[Yuji] Fushiguro.
Huh?
It's okay.
(Megumi gasps)
Looks like you've realized it.
Those who are growing wings
are forever untouchable
by the rest of us.
And that's exactly where
Itadori is standing now.
(Megumi hisses)
You die again and
I'll kill you myself!
Come on now, let's go.
Pandash!
Well alright then! I
guess I'd better not die.
I'm not going to lift
a finger to help you,
you know that, right, Itadori?
Not until you
land a Black Flash.
If you can't land a Black Flash,
then I'll just watch you die.
No matter what
happens to you. Got that?
Yes!
[Hanami] Ah, Sukuna's vessel.
And
who is that man?
He has a certain presence,
but the amount of
cursed energy he possesses
is most definitely
less than mine.
However, he has that
mysterious brazenness.
He must have
quite the technique,
since I can't move
freely before him.
So, what is this "Black Flash,"
and how will they attack?
You can talk?
That's interesting.
In that case, there's
something I want to ask you.
Are you connected with
a humanoid cursed spirit
with a patchwork face?
[Hanami] And if I say that I am?
(Yuji roars)
(water splashes)
[Hanami] He didn't
carelessly close the distance!
I commend him for that.
(Yuji grunts)
[Hanami] He's fast!
And he has more explosive
power than that girl, earlier.
However, its intensity is poor.
[Yuji] I have a wide open shot!
It's letting its guard
down because I held back!
I can land it now!
Black Flash!
(rock music)
(Todo gasps)
(Yuji yells)
[Yuji] Damn it!
(water splashes)
(Yuji gasps)
[Todo] My friend.
(Todo slaps)
Anger is a trigger
for sorcerers,
and it can work
for you both ways.
A sorcerer can be
taken down in a fight
simply because he
accidentally enraged his foe.
And the opposite is also true.
Sometimes they lose
because their own anger
disrupts their cursed energy
to the point they can't
exercise their abilities.
Your friend has gotten hurt.
And what's even worse than that,
they've rained on your
honeymoon with me,
your new best friend.
So take it from me.
I can absolutely understand
why you're boiling with rage.
But all that rage is
too much for you!
So, put it away for now.
(water running)
(Todo slaps)
[Hanami] Are they
fighting each other?
So how do you feel?
You clear-headed now?
Yeah, no stray thoughts left!
Thank you for that,
my new best friend!
(upbeat music)
[Todo] Black Flash.
It's a distortion of space,
born from the impact
of cursed energy
delivered within a trillionth
of a second of a blow.
It delivers two point five times
the force of a normal strike.
There are no sorcerers who
can consistently use Black Flash.
However,
between those who have
experienced Black Flash
and those who have not,
their distance from the
core of cursed energy
is like the distance
of Heaven from Earth!
(Yuji exhales)
[Hanami] What
tremendous concentration!
[Todo] The instant cursed
energy makes impact
within that trillionth
of a second of a blow,
space is distorted,
and cursed energy flashes black!
[Yuji] Black Flash!
(upbeat music)
(Todo chuckles)
[Todo] He's done it.
(music fades out)
(dark music)
He's done it.
Black Flash? So I did that?
What is this?
This is my cursed energy
I'm sensing, isn't it?
[Todo] Now you understand
the taste of cursed energy.
Huh?
(dark music)
Up until now,
you've just been
taking an ingredient
that you've never tasted before,
and throwing it into
a pot and boiling it,
without understanding why.
But now, after
experiencing Black Flash,
you understand the
taste of your ingredient,
your cursed energy.
You stand on a completely
different level as a chef
than you did just
three seconds ago.
So congratulations, brother.
Now you can become truly strong!
[Hanami] I had been
told that Sukuna's vessel
was immature as a sorcerer.
But he and this mysterious man,
something about them is
different from the other masses.
It can heal?
A cursed spirit is made
up of cursed energy.
Therefore, unlike us,
they don't need advanced
reversed cursed techniques
to heal their bodies.
An injury like that
would mean very
little to a special-grade.
But there's no doubt
that it shaves away
their cursed energy,
and if you crush their head,
it's game set and match.
Now!
What do you say
you and I get cooking?
[Hanami] It would seem
that perhaps
I should take you two
somewhat seriously.
-(Todo grunts)
-(Yuji gasps)
(upbeat music)
(Yuji gasps)
(Todo grunts)
(Yuji exhales)
(Yuji grunts)
Ungh! That's a
wide-ranging attack!
Don't falter!
Wide range attacks
have less speed and force.
(Yuji gasps)
(Todo grunts)
(upbeat music)
[Hanami] That hit hard!
Their blows aren't as bad as
that flashy black one before.
But each one possesses
enough force that,
if they continue steadily,
they'll damage me!
Todo! Let's coordinate
our timing better!
Yeah!
[Both] Huh?
[Yuji] Our footing!
[Todo] I messed up!
I thought it was passing cursed
energy through real objects
in order to manipulate
that much mass!
But it's all the embodiment.
The manifestation
of its cursed energy!
That's a special-grade for you!
[Hanami] Learn
how great the land is!
[Todo] Attacking while
we fall? That's brutal!
However!
[Both] Brother!
(both yell)
[Hanami] They dodged that?
But, what is this?
This strange feeling?
(water running)
[Mahito] You know, Hanami,
you should really
be more honest.
[Hanami] I don't believe
I'm faking anything.
[Mahito] I don't
mean to call you a liar.
I know why you're fighting.
But it's the process.
You should enjoy the
battles, the present,
much more than you do.
[Hanami] Do you
enjoy them, Mahito?
Well, yeah.
Although,
it was only recently
that the joy and pleasure
I feel in battle became
my main motivation.
Before I knew it,
I began tricking,
deceiving, and murdering.
And then suddenly
I felt fulfilled.
I think just as humans
eat, sleep and screw,
these things are
a curse's instincts.
As cursed spirits, we may have
gained the power of reason.
But that still doesn't justify
going against our instincts.
For everyone, the soul is a
blend of instinct and reason.
(chair creaks)
So as a result,
no one can say anything
about an individual's ratio.
But your soul is a little
constrained, isn't it?
You, Hanami,
in actuality,
you're much
stronger, aren't you?
(Yuji groans)
Todo!
I'm just fine!
(Todo grunts)
(fast music)
(Hanami lands)
(Yuji grunts)
[Yuji] It just expended
a ton of cursed energy!
(Yuji grunts)
[Todo] So now's our chance-
(Todo grunts) To strike!
You monster!
(Todo lands)
(bells chime)
(both grunt)
[Hanami] Mahito!
Right now,
I'm enjoying a fight!
I'm enjoying a fight, Mahito!
Are you good to go, brother?
(Yuji grunts)
-Yeah, you bet!
-That's excellent! Me too!
(rock music)
Then it's time to
unleash my technique!
(closing theme music)
(singing in Japanese)
(music fades out)
(upbeat music)
[Juzo and Mahito] Juju Stroll!
Coat rack!
Gonna make a
great new coat rack,
and it's gonna be so nice!
Huh?
-Hey!
-Huh?
What would Gojo end up
looking like? If you do him?
Definitely a standing rack.
I'd use his hip girdle,
with the sacral
bone and the coccyx,
as the base for the stand.
Then, I'd rework his femurs
and use them to stabilize it.
I'd use his spine's lumbar
and thoracic vertebrae
all up to the third
cervical vertebrae.
And to give it height, hey,
ancient camphor
wood would be good!
I'd use that to make
replicas of the vertebrae,
and then alternate
them with the bones
to accentuate the height.
(upbeat music)
[Juzo] Then I'd extend
the spinous process
and complete the
transverse process,
based on the overall
balance, to create the hangers.
(upbeat music)
I'd do that by grafting
on more ancient camphor.
Depending on the coloring,
it might be nice to cover
the skull with a tanned hide.
Nice, right? So very nice!
Yeah, this one could be
my best coat rack ever!
What junk!
(rock music)
(music fades out)